Masks.
This is your mask.
It's your mask, bro.
It reeks of that aphrodisiac oil
you use for your mustache.
No, man. It's Unani medicine.
It's just genetics.
We start losing hair after we hit 35.
Huh?
Why is he going towards Barakhamba?
He's gonna take a U-turn.
Seat belts.
What are you trying to do?
What are you doing?
- Out!
- Show me your hands!
- Hands up!
- Get out! Out now!
Hands up!
Where's the bag?!
Where's the bag?
Open up!
Hurry up!
Hurry up! Move it!
What's going on?
He's seen my bloody face!
Get the gun and the bag!
Hey!
Stop!
Are you alright?
I'm fine. Where's the car?
Forget the car.
We've hit the jackpot!
There's three kilograms extra!
- What?
- Look!
What's wrong with you, bro?
Oh, shit!
- Let's go to a hospital.
- No, no.
You know what
Just leave. I'll see you later.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Go on.
Sir, no mask, no entry.
That's what I'm here for.
Anything else I could help you with, sir?
Painkillers...
bandages.
Wake up! Hurry up!
We're gonna miss the breakfast, bro!
Don't "bro" me.
I'm your father, alright?
Whatever
And get ready yourself
before you dish out sermons!
"Bro"
Delhi NCR has reported a surge in...
Use your bloody hands.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Dad?
It's unhygienic. People will see.
Take this as well. Done?
And get rid of that mask.
How are you gonna eat?
Wait at the table, I'll join you.
A man was killed in a shootout
at Connaught Place.
Sources claim that the victim was carrying
some suspicious items.
The commissioner has vowed
to bring these instances under control.
The next news is from Beijing, where...
Got new kicks, Athi?
- That's nice!
- What are you doing?
You got me killed!
These are six months old.
A birthday gift from Mom and Akash.
Does he treat you alright?
That Akash?
- Excuse me, waiter?
- Yes?
- One glass of lactose-free chocolate milk.
- Yes, sir.
- And one gluten-free bread with avocado.
- Okay. Sure, sir.
- Mohit.
- Yes, sir?
Just a second, buddy.
"Lactose-free milk"?
"Gluten-free bread with avocado"?
Just give up eating instead?
-Mohit, you know what -Yes, sir?
Get him full-fat milk.
- Sure, sir.
- And just the usual bread.
Alright, sir.
Thank you, Mohit.
His name's Mohit.
What's happening to you?
Who's teaching you this nonsense?
Akash and your mom?
Just eat normal food.
You're just a kid.
- What are you doing?
- Can you just let me live my life?
Had I spoken to my father
like you just did,
he would've thrashed me.
He would've thrashed me.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
Alright, tell me something.
Why have you brought me to this hotel?
We're on a holiday, man!
- On a holiday?
- Yeah.
Which Delhite comes to Gurugram
on a holiday?
We're in the middle of a pandemic, bro.
Where do you want me to take you?
This is the best you can get, alright?
And you think I should believe you?
You should believe me.
And you should say, "Thank you."
I've been holed up
in a hotel room for 24 hours,
waiting for you to come.
We haven't even spent an hour together.
- Is this what you call a holiday?
- Come on, Athi!
Stop yapping, bro.
Watch a movie!
Order some room service!
What's your problem?
And you think room service
will make things better?
You know, it's my fault.
I made a choice to stay with you
after you separated from Mom.
I thought you'd change and all, but no.
Mom was right. You won't.
Maybe that's why she chose Akash over you.
You know what?
If you think he's better,
just like your mom does,
go and live with him.
I'm really okay with it.
You're free to go. No problem.
Whatever
Athi!
I'm sorry, man.
Riya's gonna be here in 30 minutes.
I know. Mom called me.
Let's go to a better place next week.
- We'll go go-karting.
- No, don't bother.
I'm going to Goa
with Mom and Akash next week.
- The tickets are already booked.
- Yeah, I remember.
And you don't have the time anyway.
Come on, man!
My job's really difficult.
You know that.
Bro, everyone's job is difficult!
It's not about a holiday.
It's about time.
And the way you're living
you'll be lonely someday.
Yeah, fine, I'm working on it.
And listen
I'll be late tonight.
Just order some room service, alright?
Whatever
Get some pasta, alright?
And watch a great movie!
I love you!
What the hell is he doing here?
You know him?
Yeah, he's the SP's pet.
Let's find out.
Sir, I think it was a robbery.
Seven rounds fired.
He's a bloody scumbag.
Someone's pretty mad
if they've sent him out here.
What department is he from?
Anti-corruption.
What the fruit!
And she's the bonus?
Your squeeze?
Lady Singh am.
Yes?
Alright, the eye contact
has lit up your face!
Let's look there. Come on.
Hey! Up!
- You were here when it happened, right?
- Yes, sir.
What did you see?
I've already told the department
everything I've seen!
Really?
And who do you think we are?
Pie chuckers?
Come here, a♪♪♪♪♪♪.
I'll slap the shit out of you!
Repeat it!
We're cops!
I was working the morning shift, sir.
Two men opened fire at a car.
Really?
- What did they look like?
- Who?
Your uncles.
The shooters, dumb-ass.
Did you see them?
- Yes, I did, sir.
- What did they look like?
One looked like
he was an African or a Nigerian.
And the man who ran after him
looked just like you, sir.
You think that's funny?
No, sir, I'm not kidding, he
Don't get me wrong, sir.
Please don't mind.
But he did look just like you.
Hey, CID!
Are there any CCTV cameras nearby?
Yeah, but none of those are working, sir.
- The JCBs rolled over the sewage line.
- Alright, that's enough.
- It ruined the CC...
- Yeah, alright, man!
We're grateful for your help! Stop!
We got it.
Hello? Yeah, Riya.
- I'll call you later. I'm busy.
- Stop saying foolish things like,
"He looked like you."
- Am I clear?
- What are you saying?
I've called him at least 25 times!
I've tried texting as well. No response.
I even called at the hotel room.
There's no answer.
Where is Atharv?
What is he doing here?
Sumair, please!
He must be roaming around at the hotel.
Must've left his phone behind.
- He might've gone swimming...
- Swimming pools are shut, Sumair!
And when was the last time you saw Atharv
without a phone in his hand?
Tell me honestly.
- Did you two have another...
- Hey! Don't start with it again!
There are no problems
between me and him.
We were spending some really good
father-son quality time.
- Sure.
- And he's in his space right now.
When was the last time you saw him?
11:00 a.m.
I met him for breakfast!
And you were gonna pick him up!
- It's 5:30 p.m., Sumair!
- Relax, man.
Relax, Riya.
Riya?
He's tried to run away thrice!
We always find him.
And you were the reason
he ran away thrice!
So, obviously, I can't relax!
Riya?
What's his height?
Go on, tell him.
He's...
- He's 4'8.
- Okay.
5'1.
He's 5'1.
Yeah, okay, just
write down this one.
Yeah, it's 5'1.
You're pregnant?
Yes!
Three months!
- Are you two married yet?
- No.
Why don't you do it if you're pregnant?
Oh, my God!
Can you please stay out of it
and help look for our son?
You stay out of it.
He's my responsibility. I'll find him.
Wow!
Look at you.
You're talking about responsibility?
You were irresponsible as a husband,
and you're a total failure as a father!
Are you done?
Athi, where the hell are you, man?!
Everyone's worried sick for you!
- And Riya...
- Sumair!
How are you, brother?
Sikandar.
Sikandar Chowdhary.
Sorry, who?
What can I do for you?
Don't ask obvious questions, man.
I think you know.
What is my son doing there, Sikandar?
Another obvious question!
Well, let me ask one as well.
What were you doing there?
My men have identified you, Sumair.
Morris!
He's been working for me
for the past ten years.
I had gotten him his resident visa.
And now...
he's an Aadhaar Card holder.
I had given him
a double appraisal last year.
Do you know why?
One, he doesn't lie.
And two,
he hates drugs.
Anyway, let's not beat around the bush.
I need my bag, brother.
And I know you have it.
I don't understand.
Hey, buddy!
Your dad says he doesn't understand.
Talk some sense into him.
Hello?
Hello, Atharv?
Yeah, it's me.
Are you okay?
I'm sounding okay, right?
Who are these people?
Why have they brought me here?
- I know something is going on.
- Hey, stop worrying, man.
I'm coming, alright?
Let me talk to Sikandar.
Thanks, buddy.
Yeah?
Sikandar, if you even touch my son...
Calm down, brother.
I've already touched him.
Gently, for now.
Listen to me carefully.
You know me, right?
So, don't complicate my shit.
Let's keep it simple, man.
Bring my stuff.
Take your son.
I'm sure you know the address.
See ya soon.
Jaggi!
- Can you come in for a minute, please?
- I'm coming.
Right now. Please?
What's wrong?
Get the door.
Close it.
What's wrong?
Sikandar has my son.
He's f♪♪♪ing with you.
Have you lost your mind?
I just spoke to him!
- To Athi?
- Yeah.
What are we gonna do?
What do you mean?
I'll give him the bag
and get my son out of there!
"Give him the bag"?
That's not your bag to "give".
Bro, our lives depend on it!
What the hell are you saying?
Take the damn hint, man!
There's three kilograms
of extra stuff in there!
You get these opportunities
once in a lifetime!
Stop being an emotional fool, man!
Yeah, you're right.
I'm acting like an emotional fool.
He has my bloody son!
Are you getting me?!
So, f♪♪♪ your deal!
And if you try to mess with me...
I'll f♪♪♪ you up.
Where's the bag?
Where is it?
Under the table.
Under my...
Where else could I have kept it?
This is the safest place.
Let's try and keep one kilogram at least?
We're never gonna get
this opportunity again.
Think about it!
Welcome, sir. Please come in.
Thank you.
Namaste, sir!
Sir, we'll have to check your bag as well.
- Will this do?
- Of course, sir!
Welcome, sir. Please come in.
None of them are wearing masks,
and you're worried about bags?
Sir, everyone here has been tested.
Corona stops right here.
We're conducting rapid antigen tests
with Akshay Kumar's kits!
Which kits?
Akshay's kits!
Are you here for the wedding as well?
I heard that Badshah is performing.
I'm excited!
You've tested positive.
- Me?
- No. You, sir.
- What? What rubbish?!
- Please wear a mask.
This is a false positive, alright?
Don't touch me!
You cannot go inside.
- Sir, please.
- I'm vaccinated!
Look at this, sir!
He's taking it all back to Sikandar.
He's gonna f♪♪♪ up the deal
for his bloody son.
- We had a deal! 50-50.
- Hey! Coffee!
Are you getting me, sir?
Will you shut up?
Sir, I've shot Sikandar's man.
If he finds out, he'll f♪♪♪ me up!
Shut the f♪♪♪ up!
Stop crapping your pants.
Why do you f♪♪♪ing dimwits
bite off more than you can chew?
Now if you don't shut your filthy trap.
I'm gonna write
a detailed report about you!
Sir, sir.
Listen to me carefully.
- Look at me, you dumbf♪♪♪!
- Sir.
Keep your flapper in your pants, alright?
And unless I tell you to,
I don't wanna see you move
a single muscle.
I'll handle it myself.
Hey!
Oh, shit!
What's wrong?
Reset it! Reset it, right now!
Sit!
If he calls you again,
- you're gonna give me every single detail.
- Okay.
And you had a juvenile 50-50 deal, right?
Forget about it.
It's now gonna be 60-40.
You can have 40, and I'll take 60.
With a sprinkle of
the extra three kilograms.
Keep it.
Download WhatsApp.
Break it and dump it once the job's done.
What will you do?
Break it and dump it.
Bloody dumbf♪♪♪!
Bhaisaab, they've already called us
thrice since morning.
They're on their way.
I hope it's a good night.
Yeah, tell me.
Sir, I suspected Sumair.
The cop from the narcotics team.
So, I followed him.
He's at Etlantis right now,
It's Sikandar Chowdhary's hotel.
Sir, I saw him hiding a bag
in the men's loo.
And it must be carrying cocaine
worth at least 50 crore rupees.
Aditi! Listen to me, alright?
Don't touch the bag, alright?
Don't worry, sir.
I've moved the bag.
You moved it?
Yeah, next door.
Next door?
Sir, are you gonna repeat
everything I say?
It's above the ceiling panel
in the ladies' toilet.
- Third cubicle.
- Aditi.
How long have you been
a part of the force?
Don't you know the basic rule
of investigation?
Never move the bloody evidence!
But I had to, sir!
I'm sorry. I mean...
it's not just a piece of evidence.
It's the bait.
- I can move the bag back if you like.
- No!
Look, just stay put, alright?
Or we'll be busy jerking off
with the bags,
and Sumair will get away
with all the stuff in it.
Just keep an eye on him, alright?
Yes, sir.
- I'll get there in ten minutes.
- Sure.
Who is he?
That's Sumair.
You were stressing out for no reason.
Go, get him.
Stop!
Hands up.
Raise your hands!
Turn around. Come on.
Go.
Where's my bag, buddy?
Where's my son?
Where's the rest of my stuff?
It's safe.
You'll get it when the time's right.
Where's my son?
It's safe?
I'll get it when the time's right?
Why are you in a hurry?
My delivery's been delayed
by 14 hours because of you.
I don't give a damn...
Do you now?
He just doesn't get it, man.
You know the market, right?
COVID has screwed us all.
Businesses are in shambles.
Especially, our hotel industry.
They've just opened up the lock down,
God knows for how long.
That's the reason people wanna party!
They want to get married.
Tell him, man!
Coke is like pure gold right now!
The stuff's selling
for twice its usual price!
What the hell did you think it was?
A bag of chewing tobacco?
You can just take it,
shove it in your mouth, and spit it out?
And it's all over?
I was just doing my duty.
"Doing my duty!"
"Sikandar" doesn't translate to "dumb-ass".
Bhaisaab, he's just a petty thief.
- Stop touching me!
- I'm gonna do a lot more!
Dharmesh! Dharmesh.
Come on, man! What are you doing?
Calm down, calm down.
Why are you so hyper, buddy?
Calm down.
And don't worry about him, man.
He's just recovered from COVID.
How low did your oxygen go?
Seventy-two.
But he's still breathing.
The stuff's alright.
Where's my son?
A father's maternal instincts!
It's paternal instincts, man.
- Paternal.
- Right, sorry.
Sikandar.
Where's Atharv?
He's used the name!
It's getting serious!
Go on. Call Vicky.
- Who are these men?
- Athi!
- Why have they kept me here?
- I'm here now. It's gonna be alright.
I want my phone.
- Yeah, I'll tell them!
- Hey!
Are you done?
- Vicky, take him away.
- No.
- Don't leave me here.
- Hey! Stop dragging him!
- Athi, I'm coming in three minutes!
- Hey!
- I'm coming. Three minutes, Athi!
- Alright, three minutes is good for me.
Nice jacket, man!
Did you get it at a flea market?
Go on! Get the bag!
Go on.
The bride looks just like Katrina!
There are cameras everywhere!
You'll end up getting fired
on your first day!
- A glass of water, please.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir!
- Drop it!
It looks like you guys
are having a big party in there!
Yeah, my dad's getting married
for the fourth time.
Wanna join us?
Sir?
Are you a guest at this wedding as well?
Are you married?
I'm divorced.
It's your first day, right, Bunty?
- Yes, sir.
- All the best.
Yeah, Riya, I've found Atharv.
I'll call you back
in ten minutes, alright?
Bye.
Sir. I'm sorry, sir!
Guys, the groom's family
is still dancing outside.
What's the hurry?
Let's go back inside.
You've been ready for a long time, right?
Excuse me! This is the ladies' toilet!
Oh!
Okay, thanks.
Why won't he leave?!
Calm down, you witch!
So annoying!
Sumair, why do you keep
disconnecting my call?
And how many times should I tell you
I hate voice messages?!
I'm calling you,
just answer the damn phone!
Where is Atharv?
I really hope you're not being
irresponsible like always.
Listen, just call me.
Call me now!
Or at least pick up my call, dammit!
Your daddy was gonna be here
in three minutes, right?
Well, it's been a lot
more than three minutes.
Where is he?
You think he's gonna come?
I don't know.
"I don't know"?
What does that mean?
Come on.
- Move!
- Hey, dumbf***!
Are you blind?!
Come here! Come here! Hey!
Rafa, f*** it! Let's go!
Excuse me.
Sir, your room number? Sir!
Sir, excuse me, can I help you?
This is for staff only!
Sir! Hello!
Sir, excuse me. You cannot do this!
- Sir, I need...
- Have you seen my brown bag?
- What brown bag, sir?
- A duffle bag. This big?
- No, sir. We don't have a duffle...
- Move! Move!
Sir! Where are you going?
I'll call security!
I cannot allow this, sir!
I will call security on you!
What did you say? Who're you gonna call?
I'm the bloody security, alright?
- Who am I?
- Security, sir.
Sir... Okay, okay.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry. Alright.
Hey!
- Move!
- Hey!
Come here.
- Sir?
- Listen!
- What?
- Have you seen my bag?
What bag, sir?
My brown bag!
The one you wanted to check!
Let go of my jacket.
Jacket, please.
Sorry.
Have you seen it?
I had brought it with me.
You had asked me to get it checked.
Have you seen it?
Your friends might have it, sir.
- Who?
- Sir, your friends.
A lady walked in right behind you.
And then your boss
walked in as well, right?
They showed me their ID just like you did.
You should ask them, sir.
Excuse me.
- Yeah, Sumair, what's up?
- Hey, Jaggi!
- How's your face now?
- It's alright.
- Did you find Athi?
- I'm inside Sikandar's hotel right now.
I needed you. Can you come here?
Of course, man!
You're my brother!
Of course, I'll be there.
- Is everything alright?
- Yeah, it's great.
- We'll talk after you get here.
- Yeah, alright.
- Be right there.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- Jai Hind, sir!
- What is it?
- Sir, Sumair had called me.
He's scared shit less, sir.
Sir, if he mentions my name to Sikandar...
Sikandar...
You're getting me, right?
What? You didn't know?
He's put up hoardings with your name
all over the city!
Sikandar's looking for you.
Sir, what do you want?
Do you want me to leave the city?
You don't need to be so scared, man!
What did you tell him?
Well, as you said, sir!
I told him I'd be there.
So, keep your word and get here.
And listen.
Just go with the flow, alright?
I'll teach you how you kill two birds
with a stone.
Just get here and enjoy the show.
Yes, sir. Jai Hind, sir.
PRIVATE NUMBER: DID YOU GET THE BAG?
I'M LOOKING FOR IT.
Check the f***ing CCTV, dumb-ass!
He must be in the hotel.
The CCTVs are down.
The technician's on his way.
You dumbf***s!
Are busy living in the 2G era.
Hey, Hameed!
What's wrong, darling?
Why aren't you drinking?
I'll fix you a drink.
What would you like? Scotch?
I know you're a Scotch drinker like me.
Hey, Danny!
Get some sushi for my brother Hameed.
Of course! What would you like, sir?
They're just wasting our time.
What's going on, Sikandar?
What? Your package is on the way.
You know Delhi traffic, right?
It'll be here soon. Have a drink.
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah. Absolutely!
Every TV channel's howling
about the same thing.
That was my cocaine, right?
Who was dumb enough to knick it?
Your cocaine's on the way, man!
Trust me!
- Danny, give him a taste, man!
- Yeah, of course!
It's A-one stuff, Hameed!
Right, Uncle?
Good.
Listen to me carefully, Sikandar.
I've bought the stuff for a big client.
And they've already paid me.
If I don't deliver this stuff tonight,
then you...
and your Sushi brother...
are gonna end up naked
on the streets of Connaught Place.
And do you know
where this is gonna end up?
The ding in the front...
and the dong at the back...
are gonna be out there
for everyone to see.
- Sir!
- Where's Sumair?
I don't know. He just disappeared.
Disappeared?
- I can't find him anywhere.
- Did you check the club?
Not yet.
He's a bloody alcoholic.
That's where he'll be.
Hello! Where are you going?
- Guests aren't allowed in here!
- Police! Buzz off!
Yeah, keep working.
Keep working.
What are you gawking at?
Do your job!
Move! Move!
- Hey! Stop!
- Sir!
Why did you run?
- Sir, I'll pay up!
- Why did you run?!
- Pay whom?
- The rent, sir! I'll pay it!
Sir, I've told Auntie that I'd pay
the rent in a couple of months.
I'm not gonna run. I'll pay up!
- Where are you from? Nepal?
- Nepal, sir.
Do you know the punishment
for not paying your rent?!
Sir, I couldn't pay because of COVID, sir.
Sir, the hotel was closed
and my family was starving, sir.
- I'm a genuine person, sir.
- Yeah, alright.
I make the best Chowmein!
Yeah, I get it.
Everyone loves your Chowmein.
What is it?!
Please answer my question.
What are you doing here?
- Your name's Rudraksh, right?
- Yeah.
Go cook the f***ing lentils, Rudraksh!
Listen, I need some flour.
- Flour?
- The refined flour?
Flour or refined flour?
What do you use for your bloody Chowmein?!
- I use both, sir.
- Yeah, so get it! Where is it?!
When is our bag coming?
Come on.
Come on! Get some flour!
- Hurry!
- Police.
Hey! Stop!
Why are you running?
Why is he running?!
Sir, he's my roommate.
You haven't paid the rent either, right?
Speak up!
No, sir.
Get out. I'm a cop.
- Who am I?
- Police.
Go on.
- Get the flour.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, stop!
Come back. Come here.
Come on. Get the flour!
Get me some bloody flour!
- Yes, sir.
- Come on!
Start packing!
What the hell are you doing?!
Sir, how do we pack it?
Plastic bags?
- About this big? Do you have them?
- Yes, we do.
- Yes, we do, sir.
- Good boy! Go on, get it.
- Relax.
- Will this work, sir?
- Yeah, works!
- Works?
- Come on. Start filling these up.
- Yes, sir.
- Packets of 250 grams each, alright?
- Sir, 250?
- Sir.
- Do you have a weighing machine?
- Yes, we do, sir!
- You do?
- Get it.
- Alright.
- Listen!
- Yes, sir?
Get some scissors as well.
- Scissors?
- Yeah, scissors.
And do you have some duct tape?
- Duct tape?
- Duct tape, brown tape?
- Yes, we do, sir!
- You do?
- That's my boy! Get it!
- Yes, sir.
- Sir, where should I keep it?
- Keep it.
Come on, get here.
- Hold this, and get here.
- I am, sir.
- Twenty-five packets, alright?
- Twenty-five?
Yeah, twenty-five. Good job. Come on.
- Sir.
- Come on!
- That's 250 grams?!
- Sorry, sir.
- Looks good?
- Yeah!
Twenty-one, twenty-two,
twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five.
Sir, that's it, right?
Do you have a bag?
Sir, bag.
- The scissors?
- Scissors?
There it is, sir!
Thank you, sir.
- Take this.
- No, sir!
- Take it, man!
- Sir.
- Pay your rent, alright?
- Thank you so much, sir.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- Here's your drink, sir!
- Thank you.
Sorry, sir!
You're still here?
Yeah, I have a meeting with Mr. Sikandar.
- Can you please get me some water, Bunty?
- Sure, sir.
Sikandar Chowdhary.
- It's his wedding anniversary, right?
- What are you saying, sir?
- The boss's anniversary?
- Yeah.
You know what?
I'll need a bottle of chilled champagne
and a cake in his room in five minutes.
I want you to do it!
- Me?
- Yeah, you can do it, right?
- Yes, sir. Thank you.
- Yeah?
And it's a surprise, alright?
So, just cover the bottle and the cake.
Make sure you hide it, alright?
- Of course, sir!
- Alright?
- Thank you, sir.
- You'll get the real tip upstairs.
Thank you so much, sir!
And you know what?
Get some buffed-up guys
from housekeeping as well.
We need to move some furniture.
- Can you do it?
- Yes, sir.
- You got this?
- I got this, sir!
- Yes, sir.
- Five minutes, alright?
Thank you, sir.
Your package is here, Hameed!
It's here!
I told you!
You were stressing out for no reason!
Move!
Where were you, you dumbf***?
Here you go.
Are you happy?
Get these men out of here.
Why?
The cops are swarming your hotel.
The cops? What are they doing here?
They were tipped off.
They're here for a drug bust.
A tip-off about some drugs at the party.
They're roaming around
in civilian clothes.
Get them out of here.
How do you know they're cops?
Hey, Sikandar?
Don't f*** with me, alright?
I'll rip you open right now!
Shut the f*** up, man!
You've been yapping my ear off!
F*** you, man!
This is Sikandar's home!
- The cops aren't a problem.
- They're from the narcotics department!
Ashraf and Rathore! They're scumbags!
We'll be in trouble if they raid the hotel
and find this stuff!
- Hey! Who the hell are you, man?!
- Why the hell do you care?
He's my delivery guy. He's safe.
What the f*** is wrong
with you dickheads?!
The narco cops are out there!
They'll scour through
everything in this hotel!
From your overused mouths
to your underused assholes!
I don't wanna go to jail!
- Get this joker out of here!
- Hey!
Why the f*** is he screaming?!
- Does he realize who he's talking to?!
- Who the f*** are you?
- I'm Hameed!
- Yeah, and I'm your daddy!
What the.
Narcotics department! Wanna know more?
- Hey!
Relax. I might be a narco cop,
but I'm a businessman as well.
Rafa?
Hey! Gun down.
Gun down!
Delivery boy?
From Narcotics?
Today, my respect for you.
Has grown by a couple of centimeters.
And that's your size as well, right?
Rafa, take his number.
He's gonna bring us our cocaine as well.
Hey! Who are they?
- I had warned you!
- Danny, get them out of here!
- Hey! Move! Move!
- I had warned you!
- Go on! F*** off!
- Why couldn't you just listen to me?
I'll deal with you later!
Brother, they're from the hotel staff.
What the f***? Hotel staff?
Happy anniversary, sir!
Many congratulations of the day!
Are you new here?
Yes, sir. It's my first day!
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
Have I made a mistake?
Need a hand with your furniture, sir?
My "furniture" is too big
for your hand, son.
- Let me take that.
- Sure, sir.
My anniversary is on February, 29th.
Leap year.
Every four years, alright?
Yes, sir.
Buzz off! Scram, you cockroaches!
My son, Sikandar.
Yeah, your son. Hold this.
- Yeah, tell me.
- Yeah, Vicky.
Is the package ready?
Bring him to the gaming room
in ten minutes.
Daddy's coming.
Go on.
First floor.
There's a gaming room
right across the club.
I don't want to ever see
your face again, alright?
F***ing moron.
Why can't I taste it?
Have you gotten COVID?
- Can you smell anything?
- Are you trying to be funny?
Why don't you try it, dumb-ass?
- This is flour!
- Flour?
Check the other packets!
- This is flour as well.
- Sikandar!
I'm gonna chop you up and bake you
into some delicious pies with this flour!
Open the bloody door!
Why the f*** did you lock it?!
Stay here. I'll be back.
- You look worried, Sumair.
- Not right now, Aditi!
Oh, come on!
Why are you in a hurry?
What are you doing here? Partying?
Or something personal?
I don't have time for this, Sameer.
They have my son.
That's really sad, man.
Go on!
But before you go, why don't you tell me
about the shootout at CP this morning?
How were you involved?
- What do you mean?
- Who are you working for?
Who am I working for?
I'm doing my duty!
The car that was attacked today...
was registered under the name
of Dharmesh Chowdhary.
He's Sikandar's younger brother.
And you've just walked out
of Sikandar's office,
after hiding a bag full of cocaine
in the bathroom.
You're a bloody sell-out!
Come with us!
Don't you get it?
My son is in danger, Sameer!
The whole of Gurugram is in danger because
of the amount of cocaine you're carrying.
Come on!
- Hey... Catch him!
- Hey!
Cheers! It was a close shave today.
No way, man!
He's a barker, he won't bite.
He left his
"couple of centimeters" behind.
What does that f***er think...
Ring the bell!
- He's back?
- Is he back for his ding-dong?
Hey, Sikandar! Open up!
He's swearing?
Break it down!
Yes, boss!
- Open up!
- Open it!
Don't open the door.
No, we have a long history.
I'll have to open the door.
- But, brother...
- Go on.
- What's wrong...
- You motherf***er!
What were you thinking?
Have you forgotten who I am?
Have you lost your mind?
Do I look like a f***ing pastry chef?!
You thought you'd get away with the flour?
What flour?
This flour! Go on! Eat it!
Take it and bake a f***ing cake!
You f***ing!
- There he is!
- One second, ladies and gentlemen,
are you guys having fun?
Do you want another lock down?!
- No!
Shout with me!
- Go! Go!
- Go, Corona! Go!
Happy birthday, Aisha!
- Baby, it's your birthday! Give me a kiss.
- Akhil, let me go.
Let me go, please. Akhil!
It's your birthday.
You're my girlfriend! It's okay!
No, I'm not your girlfriend.
You're drunk! Just let me go!
- Stop being such a princess!
- You're making me very uncomfortable!
- Stop it!
- You, b***♪!
Who the hell are you?
- Who is she?
- She's my girlfriend!
- My girlfriend...
- Who is she?!
- Not my girlfriend.
- No means?
- No.
Apologize.
- Sorry.
- Please leave.
- Where are you from?
- Delhi.
- From Delhi!
- Move!
Strip.
Strip!
Come on.
Strip, a♪♪hole!
Here!
Take the jacket off.
The shirt as well.
Hurry up.
Come on.
The pant!
Take it off!
Okay.
- Squat.
- What?
- Where's he?
- I don't know.
PRIVATE NUMBER: WHAT'S GOING ON?
Aditi, you should go home.
I'll handle it.
- Sir, what?
- Go home. I'll update you.
- Give me a glass of water.
- Yes, sir.
Hey!
Why so serious?
Relax, man!
Your daddy's coming to get you!
Why are you wearing this jacket?
Who are you?
Who am I?
This is me!
Hands up! Come on!
Tell me, why are you wearing this jacket?
Where did you find it?
In the bathroom.
Bathroom?
What were you doing in there?
How do you have this Police ID?
That's not mine.
I can see that, dumb-ass!
Where's this man?!
Don't be scared!
This is a fun place! Come on!
Hey, Lala!
Sheru!
Turn on the lights, man!
Lala!
Come on! Give us a smile, buddy!
Do you wanna hear my favorite song?
I'll show you.
Hey, Nafis! Give me a coin.
Sir, who is this?
Hey!
This is the bonus round of my game!
You screwed my Gucci jacket, man!
And what about my Armani?
- It was your packet!
- But it was your flour!
- No way, man. It was Sumair...
- Su...
Hey!
What the hell!
Athi.
Your delivery boy? Narcotics?
- He duped you as well?
- How can he dupe me...
- Sikandar, listen to me carefully...
- I have his son!
How can he leave without his son?
I'll call Vicky right now, man.
Your three minutes are finally up?
I've been waiting for you.
Zip it.
Yeah, brother?
Yeah, he just took his son.
What are you saying?
Hey!
Stop, you bastard!
You duped my brother!
Stop!
Out of my way!
Come on, Athi! Move!
Dad!
Hey!
Come on!
Come on! I'll teach you a lesson!
Hey!
Hey! Enough!
Hey! Don't move!
Get up!
Get lost!
Dad!
Athi!
- Dad!
- Hey, come here.
Hey!
Get up!
Look!
- Dad.
- What the...
- Hello, brother?
- Where are you?
The cop's screwing the whole gaming room!
- Where's the kid?
- I have him.
I'm gonna kill him if he hits me!
- I'm gonna kill this kid as well!
- No, you're not.
He has my bag.
Bring me the kid.
He's coming.
- Hey! Stay back!
- Dad.
I'll shoot your bloody kid! Stay back!
- Come on!
- Dad!
Dad!
- Keep moving!
- Dad!
Stop!
Athi!
Dad!
Dad.
Buzz off!
Athi!
- Dad!
- Move!
- Athi!
- Dad!
Hey!
Athi!
Dad!
Actually, I don't trust you.
You're talking about responsibility?
- We haven't even spent an hour together.
- You're a total failure as a father!
Maybe that's why she chose Akash over you.
And the way you're living,
you'll be lonely someday.
And you think room service
will make things better?
Why have you brought me here?
Don't leave me here.
Athi, I'm coming in three minutes!
Come on.
Bhaisaab, I spared him because of you.
Or I would've killed his dad!
- He's insane!
- Vicky, man! Calm down.
He's a kid.
Come here, son.
Have a seat.
Have a seat. This is your hotel.
Would you like a beverage?
Don't be shy, buddy!
Tell me. Would you like a beverage?
Hot chocolate.
With lactose-free milk.
With what?
Lactose-free milk?
Wow.
Get the kid whatever he wants.
You can order it
if we don't have it in the hotel.
Why do you take lactose-free milk?
It's healthy.
Hear that?
This is the new generation!
Intelligent!
They know what they should
and shouldn't do!
Vicky!
I'm proud of you, son.
I'm not so proud of your father.
He's a weird man!
I don't think he loves you.
In fact, I think he doesn't
even care about you.
Look, I...
I'm not a bad guy.
I'm just a businessman
who deals in cocaine.
And your father has taken
my cocaine worth 50 crore rupees.
And he won't return it.
I told him.
Give me my bag and take your son.
But no!
If I were your father, I would've
gladly sacrificed this hotel for you!
Do you know what he gave me
in exchange for your life?
Flour.
Flour, buddy!
Look!
Do I look like a bloody pastry chef?
No, right?
You guys are wasting your time.
If my dad has your drugs,
you should forget about it.
You're not gonna get it back.
This kid...
What the f*** is happening here?!
Call Morris.
What a cocky kid.
Morris?
Yeah, come inside.
Look at me!
I've worked really hard
to build this 7-star hotel.
You and your father...
are putting me off-balance.
Do you know who I was
before I built this hotel?
A butcher.
If your dad doesn't get me my bag
in an hour,
I'll send you back to him in a bag.
In kheema-form.
You know what kheema is?
Minced meat!
Take him away, man.
Give him his bloody lactose-free milk.
Come on. Let's get you
some lactose-free milk.
Morris.
Find that bastard! Now!
Yes, boss.
Why are you still here?
I had asked you to leave, right?
I won't leave till I get him, sir!
Aditi, I know that man, alright?
He's a shrewd man!
He must've duped us already
and gotten away.
No, sir. The dope in that bag
is worth 50 crore rupees.
He won't leave without it.
You know what?
Just go home!
This is an order.
Police!
- Have you seen anyone in a dark gray suit?
- No.
He just came in!
No, ma'am.
Shit!
- Have you seen anyone?
- No, ma'am.
- Have you seen him?
No one came here! I swear!
Sumair, what the hell are you doing?!
Where's my bag, Aditi?
Back off, Sumair!
I know you're working for Sikandar!
You're the rat in the department.
I don't have the time for this, Aditi!
Where's my bag?!
I know the truth about you!
There's no coming back from here.
I know who you are...
I've been working undercover
for the past two years...
to bust this drug racket
and you f***ed it up for me!
Where's the bag?
The shootout at CP this morning,
I had set it up!
I asked Jaggi to accompany me
because he's been f***ing dirty for years!
Look at me!
He's working for a senior cop!
And that's the guy I need to get,
you understand?
You understand?!
F***ing liar!
I'm a liar?
I'm a liar, huh?
Liar?
- Who is he, Aditi?
- I don't know.
- Who is he? Who is he, Aditi?
- I don't know!
- You know him, Aditi!
- Atharv.
Atharv!
He's my f***ing son!
And Sikandar has him!
I don't know what the f***
he's doing to him!
And if he gets hurt because of you chumps,
I'll f*** y'all up!
- I'll f*** you up!
- You're hurting me, Sumair. Stop it!
Ladies' toilet.
Third cubicle.
Exactly where you had kept it.
I can't believe you don't trust me.
You have no idea.
That the roots of the corruption
in this department go all the way up.
We're just pawns.
The real game, it's up there.
I'm sorry.
- Did a cop show up here?
- No, sir!
- Are you lying?
- No, sir, I'm not.
Tell me the truth, or I'll...
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Shut up!
- What?
- Bhaisaab, the staff had called.
He's behind the kitchen.
Alright.
Behind the kitchen. Let's go.
Where's the key?
Where's the key to these handcuffs?
In the pocket.
"In the pocket."
Of course, it's in the pocket, dumbf***!
How did you get my ID?
How?
I'm gonna keep your car.
Which one do you drive?
Walk home, f***er!
I would like to raise a toast...
to my amazing husband!
Thank you for always protecting me.
Thank you for always being there
with me when things got rough.
Hey! Stop!
In all our difficult times...
you always stood by my side.
You are my rock.
Cheers!
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Who's this guy?
What's going on?
Is this someone you know?
Papa? What's happening?
Who are you?
Congratulations.
You f***ing...
Have you lost your bloody mind?
These are my hotel's guests!
You'll ruin my business!
Put it away!
What's happening?
- Oh, my goodness!
- Oh, man!
Stop it!
Oh, my goodness!
Hey, stop it!
Oh my God!
Guys, Badshah's here!
Badshah's here!
It's okay.
Sweetheart, don't cry, please.
Please, I'm extremely sorry.
We didn't realize that
a goon had entered our hotel.
We're trying to nab him.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
See, Badshah...
Badshah is here.
Get up, buddy.
Take care of her, alright?
And have a great evening.
Because I'm not having one.
Sir, it's piping hot.
Sir, careful.
- See, the vegetables have gone under it.
- I'll get them, sir.
Aditi.
Are you alright?
I should be asking you that.
- What are you looking at?
- No, sir. Nothing.
Hey, stop!
Stop.
Why aren't you answering your phone, man?!
What the f***!
They've thrashed you.
Sir, did he thrash you a lot?
Sumair has gone rogue
in our department, Aditi.
Sir, I'm not completely sure about that.
What do you mean?
He told me that he was
working undercover...
to expose a senior officer
from the department...
who's the center of this drug nexus.
And Jaggi works for that officer.
Did you get it?
I've spent the past ten years of my life
chasing corrupt officers like him!
This is what they all say
when they're caught.
"I was working undercover."
Sumair is a threat to our department.
I know where the bag is.
You're worried about the bag?
Where's Athi?
If I see him now...
I'll take him down personally.
He's toying with you.
Trying to manipulate you.
Keep your personal shit aside
and use your brain.
Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm alright.
Come on.
Yeah.
Brother!
Let's go through the back.
Yeah, why not?
I'll clean up and come.
You stay here.
- Who is it?
- Personal.
Jaggi!
PRIVATE NUMBER: WHERE ARE YOU?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO CALL YOU FOR AGES!
WE DON'T HAVE THE TIME, JAGGI.
DID YOU REACH THE HOTEL?
DID YOU FIND SUMAIR?
I can still save your life.
Yeah?
I'll be back.
Rafa.
Just stay here and give me your gun.
- Bhaisaab?
- Just stay here!
Give me the gun. I'll be back.
Give me the gun.
Come on.
You're making a big mistake, delivery boy.
Where's my son, Sikandar?
- I'll shoot him!
- Go on! Shoot!
- Kill me!
- Yeah, go ahead!
You and your son can go to hell!
- Shoot! Are you f***ing scared?
- Shut up!
- Shoot him! He wants to die!
- Hey, Sikandar!
I know this is your plan!
He's working with you
- and you wanna take all my stuff!
- Shut up!
Shut up! You've been
chewing my ear off all evening!
- Shut up!
- I've made you what you are!
He was a small-time dope peddler
at Majnu's shop!
I turned the business white!
Coke was my f***ing idea!
Balls, it was your idea!
- I've taken this business from you!
- Hey, shut up!
- You're a f***ing pimp!
- Ask your wife who the real pimp is!
Ask her why your daughter
doesn't look like you!
- Quiet!
- And you know that smokin' tattoo
on her left thigh?!
- That was my idea as well!
- Shut the f*** up!
Hey, I'll shoot you!
Flour? Really?
Where's my son?
Shit!
Jaggi!
Look, I don't have the time for this.
Tell me where the bag is,
or I swear on my kids' lives
I'll kill your son.
Check the car.
There's one more dead body here.
Fuck!
Jaggi! Jaggi, where's my phone?
Where's my phone, you dumbf***?!
Sumair... Sumair has it.
Sumair.
- Hospital! Hospital!
- Yeah.
- Hospital.
- I'll take you to a hospital.
F***ing dumbf***!
Did you find anything?
Flour.
Oh, my God! It's a ladies' toilet!
Sorry, ladies.
This is my hotel.
Problem with plumbing.
Please continue.
Where is it?
Get it!
Are you f***ing with me again?
Get the bag!
Boss!
Boss, get up.
Do you have kids?
One. He's one year younger than you.
So, I'm guessing this is
how you treat him as well.
What do you mean by "this"?
What are you doing, Danny?
He's a kid!
He's getting smart with me.
Don't grow up to be
a man like your father, alright?
Come on, Vicky!
My mood is ruined.
Let's get a drink.
Pick up! Pick up!
Please, Dad! Pick up!
- Hello?
- Dad! It's me.
Whose phone is this, Athi?
Sikandar's brother.
They've just gone out.
They're threatening me, Dad!
What?
Yes, Dad.
Did anyone hit you, son?
Sikandar's brother hit me.
Sikandar said if you don't
return the bag in an hour,
he'll chop me into pieces.
Dad, you'll come for me, right?
I'm really scared.
Of course, son!
Are you sure you will come?
You're my world, sweetheart.
You mean everything to me, Atharv.
Now, be strong, okay?
Be strong.
Please come soon, Dad.
Daddy's coming.
Bro, this drink. Over there.
Yeah, thank you.
Get me some ice, Bunty.
Sir, you really screwed me today.
It isn't the boss's anniversary.
Can't you see?
I'm equally screwed!
Sir, your face looks like shit!
- Give me some ice and fix me a drink.
- Sure.
- Single malt.
- Yes, sir.
Hello? Yeah, we need backup.
- A glass of water, please.
- Yes, ma'am.
Immediately! There's been a shootout!
Emerald Etlantis Hotel, MG Road.
Got it?
Yeah.
- Okay and send an ambulance as well.
- Hello?
We have two casualties.
Yes, sir. On the way.
Yes, I'm on my way.
Okay, listen, hurry up!
Hurry up.
Who's drinking milk at a bar?
It's for the boss's brother.
People are drinking hot chocolate
on a Saturday evening!
And the one with lactose-free milk!
I wasted two hours looking for this milk!
Sir, may I please go?
We've been guarding this place
for so long.
Well, it's our job.
Hi.
Please open the gate.
Hello, sir!
Where should I keep it?
- Keep it there.
- Okay, sir.
There's your lactose-free chocolate milk.
Drink up.
Buh-bye.
You look like a good kid
from a decent family.
This isn't the right place for you.
Go on. Leave.
Stay back, Athi.
Dad!
Dad! Dad, get up!
You shouldn't have hit my son.
- Where's my bag?
- Dad!
Danny!
- Danny!
- Where's my bag?
Dad!
Danny, open up!
- Danny!
- Answer me!
- Where's my bag?
- Are you here for me or for the bag?
- Vicky!
- Athi, get out of here!
No, I won't! Answer me!
Are you here for me
or for the bag full of drugs?
Bhaisaab, hurry!
Listen to me, alright?
I'm your father! And I need to do my job.
Not getting the bag
will mess everything up!
Get out of here.
I'll explain later.
Go on! Hurry!
Break it.
Hey!
Danny! Vicky!
Be it the father or the son,
fire at will.
We'll find the son first, Bhaisaab.
He has my phone.
I'm tracking the brat.
Badshah! Badshah!
Ladies and gentlemen!
All you people of Gurugram...
please welcome, the Bad Boy.
Badshah!
Hey! How long is it gonna take?
I'm working on it, sir.
Just give me a minute.
Dad!
Athi, come on!
Sir, done.
Just hold on to my hand, alright?
- Get him from the back.
- Yes.
Bhaisaab, I'm here!
Sir, I've found Sumair. Service corridor.
Where are you?
Right behind you.
Where are you going?
Wait!
Let them fight.
We'll arrest the mongrels who survive.
You get that?
What's going on?
Hey! Come here!
- What's wrong?
- Fire alarm.
Get out of here.
And call for backup. Quick!
Where did he go?!
Stop! Stop!
What are you doing, Dad?
Let's go!
- Hurry up!
- Wait a second!
What will you do with the gas cylinders?
Let's go!
- Unlock it, Dad!
- It isn't working!
Whose keys are these?
Whose car is that?
That's the one! Come on!
Whose car is it?
Wait.
I'll explain everything. Just get in.
Run! Come on.
Sit! Seat belt?
Vicky, get the bag.
- Let's go, brother.
- Check it to be sure.
It's alright.
You f***er!
- You killed my brother!
- Gun down!
- Hey!
- Drop the gun!
Hold fire!
Don't shoot!
Vicky!
Sumair, stop! I said, stop!
It's over, Sikandar.
Let's go.
Listen, Athi.
- I need you to promise me something.
- Not now, Dad.
Please, just drive.
Say you promise me.
I promise.
Whatever happened tonight...
you're not gonna tell anyone about it.
No, I won't.
Nobody means nobody.
Take the phone out of my pocket.
Answer your phone.
It's your phone.
It's Jaggi's phone.
Check his messages.
PRIVATE NUMBER: WHERE ARE YOU
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO CALL YOU FOR AGES!
WE DON'T HAVE THE TIME, JAGGI.
DID YOU REACH THE HOTEL?
DID YOU FIND SUMAIR?
Answer the phone, Jaggi!
He knows that we're the center
of this drug nexus.
And that we work for Sikandar.
Take him behind the hotel
and just kill him.
Keep driving! Eyes on the road!
Good job.
It's been a long night, huh?
Yeah, it's been a very long night.
Wear your seat belt.
Seat belt.
Eyes on the road! Keep driving!
Dad!
- Please don't fall asleep, Dad.
- Sorry.
Athi!
I know you think that...
I'm irresponsible.
That I don't have time for you.
And that I don't care.
The last one isn't true, son.
I care.
I care a lot, son.
Sir! Sir!
- What happened, sir?
- What happened?
Sikandar shot everybody!
Come, sir.
Easy.
This man!
He's still taking things lightly, Athi.
Just look at him.
But this man is the light of my life, Mom.
Easy, man.
Looking nice.
You and your sarcasm.
No, I'm serious.
Akash, I need a favor, man.
We left our car at the hotel, so...
if you don't mind,
can you drop us there?
- Of course. Let's go.
- Thanks.
So, Athi, what plans now?
You're coming with me
and Akash to Goa, right?
No, Mom. I have plans with Dad.
What plans?
Staycation, right?
Dad, you promised!
Of course!
Sorry.
We have plans.
Thanks. Bye.
Bye.
Sumair!
Hey, Super cop!
Why are you still following me?
I took a bullet for you.
Well, you did it for the medal.
But on a serious note,
I'm really sorry about that day.
Me too.
- Glad to see Atharv's alright.
- He's fine.
Thanks.
There's gonna be an inquiry next week
about the missing three extra kilograms.
Yeah, three extra kilograms.
You'll be there for that, right?
Yeah, of course.
Of course, I'll be there.
Great.
Sameer is just a fish in the pond.
There are many like him in the department.
Yeah, and we'll catch them together.
- Yeah!
- Alright, take care.
- I'll see you around.
- Bye.
What's wrong?
What are you looking at?
Are you ready for your holiday?
Let's go?